
[1] 

[2] Kate manages to make her way out of the wolf encirclement, and she tries to retreat, in the hopes that some of her teammates will finally grow a backbone and help her flank the enemy that is now focusing on her, exclusively. Surprisingly, a few of the other gladiators get the hint, and they approach the creatures from behind, while they are distracted, managing to actually kill four of them, before the wolves and the lions are forced to change their tactics.

Now that Kate's teammates have finally joined the battle, and that the wolves and lions have scattered, it doesn't take the gladiators long until they hunt down their remaining enemies, and finish them all off.


[3] "I understand," Kate says.

"Then prepare to clear the fighting area," the owner says. "The next fight will begin shortly."

As the owner turns to leave, Kate and the others also head towards their division area, while the warriors of the sixth division are preparing to enter the battlefield.

